{
"time":
{
"minutes":20,
"seconds":00,
},
	"title": "JavaScript Quiz",
	"submitURL": "lib/com/fahimchowdhury/submit.php",
	"grades":
	[
	{
	"max":59,
	"grade":"FAILED",
	"message":"<p>You have <span class='grade'>FAILED</span> the Quiz.</p><p>Your JavaScript level is: <br><span class='level'>LEARNER</span></p>"
	},
	{
	"max":75,
	"grade":"PASS",
	"message":"<p>Your grade is a <br><span class='grade'>PASS</span>.</p><p>Your JavaScript level is: <br><span class='level'>JUNIOR</span></p>"
	},
	{
	"max":85,
	"grade":"MERIT",
	"message":"<p>Your grade is a <br><span class='grade'>MERIT</span>.</p><p>Your JavaScript level is: <br><span class='level'>MID-WEIGHT</span></p>"
	},
	{
	"max":100,
	"grade":"DISTINCTION",
	"message":"<p>Your grade is a <br><span class='grade'>DISTINCTION</span>.</p><p>Your JavaScript level is: <br><span class='level'>SENIOR</span></p>"
	}
	],
	"questions": [
		{
			"id": 0,
			"type": "radio",
			"question": "what is a Scope?",
			"answers": ["Something you look through", "the current window","the current tab","the current location in the script"]
		}, {
			"id": 1,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you write an empty Singleton class?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}, {
			"id": 2,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you encapsulating code?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		},
		{
			"id": 3,
			"type": "radio",
			"question": "How do you attach an 'onload' event to the window in IE 8 and below?",
			"answers": [" window.addEventListener(\"load\", onLoad);", "window.attachEvent(\"onload\", onLoad);","window.addEventListener(\"onload\", onLoad);","window.attachEvent(\"load\", onLoad);"]
		}, {
			"id": 4,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "How do you create a div element and store it in a variable called 'myDiv' then append it to the body?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		},
		{
			"id": 5,
			"type": "radio",
			"question": "How do you attach an attribute to a DOM element?",
			"answers": ["myDiv.setAttribute(\"index\",123456);", "myDiv.index=123456","myDiv.createAttribute(\"index\",123456);","myDiv.index(123456);"]
		},{
			"id": 6,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you add a class name to a DOM element which is named 'myDiv'?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}, {
			"id": 7,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you change the width of a DOM element which is named 'myDiv'?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		},{
			"id": 8,
			"type": "radio",
			"question": "How do destroy an object (Garbage Collection)?",
			"answers": ["test = null", "test = undefined","destroy test","delete test"]
		}, {
			"id": 9,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you write an empty instance class which is named 'Car'?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}, {
			"id": 10,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you write an inheritable variable called 'width' in a class called 'Shape'?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}, {
			"id": 11,
			"type": "radio",
			"question": "how do you parse a JSON object in IE?",
			"answers": ["JSON.parse(jsonString);","eval('(' + jsonString + ')');","parseJSON(jsonString);","eval( jsonString );"]
		}, {
			"id": 12,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you parse 25.5 as an integer?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}, {
			"id": 13,
			"type": "code",
			"question": "how do you check if an object called 'name' is a type of a String?",
			"answers": [],
			"tip":"Note: Don't forget the semi-colon!"
		}
	]
}
